- If
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): you don't pay close attention to Joe Biden, you're probably content to dismiss him as just a senile old fool who's exiting the
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): stage at high
speed. But
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): if you actually listen to him, if you watch what Joe Biden says, it dawns on you, actually, this man is evil,
Speaker 3: actually evil.
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): Listen to what he says. It's dishonest, it's vicious, it's cruel to his fellow Americans. He's a bad person and he's the president of the United States. And yet no one seems to say that out loud or even notice.
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): Instead, our moral superiors, our overlords, are very exercised about, well, some people you've probably not even heard of.
People on the
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): internet who are saying true things. And one of the people who makes them maddest is a guy, really an account, called Cat Turd. Yes, that's the name, one word, on X, formerly Twitter. Cat Turd has millions of followers and is remarkably, remarkably controversial
about...
for
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): a person whose name has never been spoken in public. He actually got into a fight with Adam Kinzinger, no less than Adam Kinzinger. Speaking of evil, here's, in case you've forgotten it, here's what it looked like.
Speaker 4: Kinzinger made that clear the other day when he responded personally to a Twitter account called Cat Turd. Because when you're one of Washington's leading authorities on foreign policy, you spend a lot of time on Twitter reading accounts with names like Cat Turd.
Speaker 4: So the other day, Kat Turd made the mistake of posting a meme that seemed to mock the colors of the Ukrainian flag. Colors that are sacred to Adam Kinzinger and every other empathetic soccer mom in her mid-40s. You can imagine how offensive that was. It was like telling an off-color joke about Meghan Markle. It could not stand.
And so
Speaker 4: alone and battling debilitating hot flashes in his kitchen, fighting the urge to open yet another bag of chips Ahoy, Adam Kinzinger fought back.
Speaker 5: Literal evil, he wrote in a late night response to Cat Turd. If I met you in person, it would not
Speaker 4: end well for you, sicko. Hear that, Cat Turd? It will not end well for you.
Speaker 4: that's not a pillow fight Adam Kinzinger is talking about that's a full-on slap fight with hair pulling this is real you'd better apologize our heart
goes out to
Speaker 4: cat turd tonight who's probably cowering in a litter box somewhere waiting for Adam Kinzinger to show up with sharpened
nails so
Speaker 6: cat turd
Speaker 7: enraged Adam Kinzinger
Speaker 7: And it's also been noticed on late night comedy shows. Watch.
And
Speaker 8 (higher-pitched voice): things seem to hit a new low last night as he retweeted three times an account called Cat Turd.
Now, to
Speaker 9: be fair, the
cat is wearing
Speaker 8 (higher-pitched voice): glasses, so it must be smart. The
actual Twitter
Speaker 8 (higher-pitched voice): handle for the account is Cat Turd 2.
And
Speaker 8 (higher-pitched voice): I, for one, cannot wait to see what's in store from Cat Turd 3.
Speaker 10: Cat Turd sounds like
Speaker 8 (higher-pitched voice): someone Joe Biden would have brought up in a speech during the primaries. Oh, when I was growing up in Scranton, there was a real mean son of a gun. We used to call him Cat Turd. He
could doo-wop
Speaker 8 (higher-pitched voice): and bebop like nobody's business. What was I talking about? Oh, yeah, climate change.
well
Speaker 11: there's a reason nobody watches
Speaker 12: late night comedy shows anymore but still cat turd seems to offend people why is that who is this man who's cat
turd one well
Speaker 12: we found him he's a man he's from the south that's all we know he wants to keep his name private because he doesn't
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): want his life any more disrupted than it already has been but he is joining us anyway in physical form catcher it's great to see
Speaker 13: you how you
doing
Speaker 13: You made it, Tucker. So many questions. I actually
Speaker 7: don't know your real name, just for the record. Okay. What year did you graduate from Yale?
Speaker 14: Yeah, I graduated Yale, I think, 1984. No,
Speaker 15: seriously.
Speaker 16: I'm guessing you didn't go to Yale, and I mean that. I
went to Harvard after
Speaker 16: Yale. You
went
Speaker 7: to Harvard.
Speaker 7: I remember you so well there. What was your preparation for being captured? Tell us your life trajectory. Who are you without revealing your
name? Well, I'm
Speaker 17: from northwest Florida, I mean, Georgia. Same thing. Yeah. Well, I live in northwest Florida now. But so I graduated high school kind of early at 17, joined the Army. I was telling you earlier.
Speaker 17: I spent my 18th birthday in a foxhole in Fort Dix, New Jersey in basic training, back when it really was basic training. And then I got injured when I was over in Bad Kissigan, Germany, and we were on alert, and I hurt my back real bad and had surgery. And that was pretty much the end of my Army career. I was medevaced back to Fort Gordon, Georgia, had back surgery. I actually tried to stay
in, but...
they
Speaker 18: wouldn't
Speaker 19: let me yeah i mean it's been something i've had to deal with my whole life
Speaker 20: so they wrecked your body then kicked you
Speaker 19: out yeah good okay you know it was an honorable
Speaker 21: medical discharge but
yeah
Speaker 19: and so um after
Speaker 22: that um i hitchhiked to panama city and i've pretty much been in in
Speaker 17: the panhandle ever since you know i'm 59 years old um i spent you know just like
Speaker 23: most people
i
Speaker 17: was
Speaker 17: I'm
Speaker 23: different than most of the influencers that do all the right things, have the kids, wear the suit and ties. I pretty much was screwed up until
I was
Speaker 24: about 40, 45 years old. I had a couple of failed marriages, followed by, I was a professional
Speaker 23: musician for a year. I was a hippie. I had long hair and a beard and smoked weed and had a VW
Speaker 14: van and wore three-dyed shirts. I
Speaker 23: did. I did. I was a real hippie.
Speaker 23: I went from job to job. Partied a lot. Yeah, I partied a lot. I had my stint with drugs and alcohol. And, you know, I don't know why everybody's scared to admit it. You know, everybody paints this big famous picture, you know, this big picture of how, you know, in the world that we live in today. It's just like, I just, I've always been honest with my followers and on my podcast. I don't trust people who don't
Speaker 27: know how weak they are.
Speaker 23: Yeah, I know.
Yeah.
Speaker 23: And so I kind of aimlessly went through my life and then I finally ended up, you know, working a good fiber optics job for years. At 54 years
old, which was
Speaker 23: five years ago, I'd never been on social media. I didn't know anything about social media. I didn't even know how it worked. I had no friends on social media and I just decided to I got arthritis in my fingers. I couldn't play guitar anymore. And I was just like, you know what I'm going to do? I'm just going to get on Twitter.
Speaker 23: And I just saw the cat, just said cat turd. I never thought I'd have a hundred followers. You know, who would think that it's just like, it's like Homer Simpson now, cat turds.
Speaker 29: It's way beyond me, you know, they're doing.
- Wait, if
Speaker 30 (lower-pitched voice): I could just ask
you to pause, what
Speaker 30 (lower-pitched voice): was the moment when you decided to make that your numb to gear?
- I
Speaker 31: just was like surfing
Speaker 22: through the web and I saw that cat picture and it just, cat turd. It was that simple.
Speaker 22: I mean, you know, I didn't think anybody was ever going to follow me. I remember asking people for weeks, how do I post a picture on here?
And so I don't even
Speaker 22: know how it took off. It just got legs somehow,
Speaker 23: and it just took off.
So, but
Speaker 23: why did you do it?
Why did I do what? Why
Speaker 32: did you go online and start giving your opinions? I don't
Speaker 22: know. Well, I've always been, as a professional musician in the 90s,
Speaker 23: you know, you have to be good at construction.
Speaker 23: construction
Speaker 33: yeah because you got to make money yeah no you're not gonna make
Speaker 24: it i'm a little slow i missed that so you better learn to build stuff so you know me and my band guys we were we were
Speaker 22: builders you know we built decks ruse built up built a house whatever and so in the 90s uh you you're bored and you know we played
Speaker 34: music at night we didn't want to listen to music so i started listening to rush limbaugh
-
Speaker 35: Really? - So every day we'd listen to Rush Limbaugh while we were
Speaker 22: building houses, whatever. - You
and
Speaker 36: every construction crew in America.
Speaker 22: - Yeah, and it just like, I didn't even know, I was a hippie. I thought I was a liberal. I didn't know what I was still. And I was like, this guy's saying everything I believe. And it was, you know, I listened to him to the day he died. - Really? - Yeah, total Rush baby.
And
Speaker 22: it was just like, this guy's talking exactly what I think. And I never even knew what I was until I started listening to him. But that's how I got in. And I was just a political junkie from the first time I heard him. And it's just been like that ever since. So I got on Twitter, now X, and just started posting.
And man,
Speaker 22: what a
Speaker 37: five years.
Speaker 12: - That's unbelievable. - It is.
But
Speaker 12: why did you do that? I mean, a lot of people have political opinions, but they don't imagine that other people want to
Speaker 38: read them. Or they don't feel compelled to share them with the world on a social media app.
Speaker 39: I don't
Speaker 37: know why it caught fire. But why did you want to do it? Because you were frustrated? Yeah, I guess so. I just, you know, I think as
Speaker 22: artistic, although I didn't play on stage a lot in the last years, I would always go to my room and I wrote a lot of music. I actually wrote my best stuff then.
and
Speaker 22: it was just i need that artistic outlet yes and when i lost that i was really kind of depressed because i'd lost my fingers it's like overnight they started swelling up i got arthritis from playing guitar and using power tools my whole life and um i was just like i just need to do something and so i just got on social media just it's just
Speaker 23: the spur of the moment it was my birthday it was like two days after my birthday i said i'm gonna join twitter
And I
Speaker 22: was asking people, I was calling people, how do you join Twitter? How do you do a picture? Is
there a
Speaker 41: membership committee? What's the rules? So at what point
did it, I
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): can't remember the first time I saw it, but at what point did you realize it was working?
Speaker 42: I
don't
Speaker 41: know. I remember after two or three months, I was working
Speaker 22: on a job in Miami, and I told one of my friends that was rooming with me at the time, we were working there.
Speaker 22: I said, man, this thing's really taken off. And he thought I was crazy. He said, what? And I said, this cat turd thing. And he thought I was nuts. Because everybody did. And I was trying to tell everybody, this thing's really taken off. And everybody's just like, whatever. Here's the shovel.
Start
Speaker 43: to get the rocks over there in that hole.
And it just
Speaker 22: caught fire. I don't know how. I don't know how it did. And it just keeps going.
Speaker 30 (lower-pitched voice): Wow. I
Speaker 11: mean, so you're in Miami rooming with another guy that you're working with. Yeah.
- On
Speaker 11: some kind of job.
Speaker 44: - Yeah, fiber optics job. I did fiber optic
Speaker 45: construction for years after I got finished with my music career.
-
Speaker 46: And like, at the point that Adam Kinzinger starts replying to
Speaker 30 (lower-pitched voice): you and threatening your life. - Oh yeah. - By the way, that would be quite a slap fight. Do you feel confident you
Speaker 39: could win? - I
Speaker 19: don't know, you know,
it's...
Speaker 19: He's scary. I
want to see eye
Speaker 19: to eye with him, so I'm going to go get a Home Depot five-gallon bucket so he can stand on it.
But when Adam
Speaker 47: Kinzinger himself, he's got Ukraine to defend. Oh,
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): yeah. He's super busy transitioning or whatever he's doing. When he takes time to attack you
Speaker 48: and threaten to beat you up or scratch you,
Speaker 49: yeah like and that wasn't my meme i just said i think i said i shouldn't be laughing at this but it's funny
Speaker 22: yeah and then um and then it made it worse you know once he does that that he he don't understand how the internet works now they got his face on it yeah you know what i mean now now all the time you see that meme it's his face on it now well how do you understand how the internet works
Speaker 12: i don't know i just somehow do
interesting
Speaker 37: yeah so what has it done to your life well it's It's totally changed my life.
Speaker 22: you know financially i started selling merch and then i got a podcast you know we got uh jules and i have a co-host jules jones our podcast is called in the litter box and you know we got a deal with rumble which we love we love rumble and um and then you know fast forward to these ad shares which are crazy you know with elon musk i mean it's big money and um
I
Speaker 22: bought a new truck a couple of weeks ago. I never had a new vehicle with
Speaker 51: my wife, you know, and to be able to do something like that for me. I mean, I think a lot of people, I know
Speaker 22: what it's like to live paycheck to paycheck for most of my life. I know what it's like to live like a teabag, you know, at the end of the work day and be so sore. I know what it's like to choose from your rent and food. I know what it's like to...
Speaker 22: I ride around on four different tires. One's got three plugs. One's got
Speaker 19: five plugs. One's got 13 plugs in it. You know, we call them baloney skins, no tread. So I think a lot of people
Speaker 22: just – I'm kind of like the Rudy of Twitter. I probably don't deserve to be there, but I worked
Speaker 52: hard enough to maybe get that one play at the end of the game.
Speaker 52: It's the most American story ever.
It
Speaker 54: really is nuts. It really is nuts. I don't think there's a lot of people like
Speaker 22: my situation because, like I said, most of the influencers are, I mean, they just, they've, and they did the right thing. Not me. I did the wrong thing. They did the right thing. They've got great wives and kids, and, you know, they've made a lot of money. They've got, you know, parents that are successful, and they went to college. For sure. And I'm just a working class stiff.
Speaker 56: Well,
Speaker 56: that's the ruling class of the country yeah
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): and I'm from it so I know I know yeah so it's pretty amazing to see this happen to you
Speaker 12: it is so how much of your day is spent on
it
Speaker 22: pretty much seven days a week I'm an insomniac always had been so I give it four or five and I basically
do
Speaker 57: it seven days a week 15 hours a day
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): what is so but you're you spent your life
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): moving physically moving outside obviously it's been hard on your body as you said oh
Speaker 58: it has
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): but it's also there's something good about moving and i mean what's it like the change at 55 to go from you know being on the road installing fiber cable to sitting behind a screen all day
Speaker 41: oh it's fantastic screw moving no but
Speaker 59: well sorry that's
Speaker 19: so awesome i've i've got you know i
Speaker 22: i
Speaker 22: I've got 13 rescue pets and I still take care of my... I got a horse ranch, but there's no horses. It's got a barn and the whole deal. And it's fenced in where my dogs can run free and I chase them around all day. - 13 rescues? - Yeah, 13 now.
Speaker 60: - What's that like?
Speaker 22: Well I post all the pictures online and it's all these beautiful pictures but they don't see all the fights and the growling and
Speaker 19: he's swallowing a bone and he's swallowing a rope and they're all chasing a squirrel and they're fighting and they don't see all that. I don't know
what
Speaker 22: happened but they just started coming to me. I've never been to a rescue shelter. I found all of my pets that.
Speaker 22: Uh, starving and beaten and abandoned and, uh, and just on the side of the road, all the dogs, except I got two
Speaker 19: puppies. One of the dogs
I got,
Speaker 19: uh, uh, came in and she was young. I didn't think anything about it and she got pregnant and before I knew it, it was just
like, I
Speaker 19: had 10
Speaker 51: puppies too on top of this. And it's funny cause I gave them away and they got Twitter accounts. They got huge Twitter accounts. People follow the puppies. They're called
puppy turds.
- Why do
Speaker 37: you adopt so many animals?
Speaker 22: - I just, I mean, when you see a dog starving, what are you gonna do? And then I try to tell myself, I'm gonna re-home
some of
Speaker 22: these. And then you spend so much time with them trying to just like get them fed. - Yeah. - They're so, the ones I find, they're so almost dead, starving to death. So, and then I fall in love with them. I can't let them go. And it's that
simple.
Speaker 60: - Wow.
Speaker 62: i mean that's pretty um that's pretty amazing
Speaker 63: but
Speaker 44: i
gotta stop well now
Speaker 44: you can afford the dog food yeah so um
Speaker 64: i can and um i've you know it's just
Speaker 22: kind of turning thing where people say hey cat turd i got a rescue we found on the side of the road so i'll post it or i'll repost it and it's just turned into something i do i've had kennels
built
and you
Speaker 22: got to keep them separated. Some of them, you know, they're from, some of them I find they're 10 years old. Some I find they're puppies and some of them just don't like each other.
Speaker 65: Yeah. Dogs are like that. It's hard to get pack cohesion. So
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): you're not telling us your real name or taking your glasses off, which I respect, but tell us why. Tell us why that would be a concern in a supposedly free country.
Speaker 22: Yeah. So number one, I like being in the background. I get invited to all the red carpet events
and stuff,
Speaker 22: but i never go it's just not my thing uh but i
Speaker 66: mean for just saying my opinion and that's all i do i just give my opinion i just
Speaker 22: like look at each issue and
they call me
Speaker 22: a right-wing fanatic on wikipedia and you know all these hit pieces they do but you know i hate the republican and democrat party equally me too i mean we have a country now 99 of washington dc is just corrupt and um
Speaker 22: we're the resist you're not the resist you know the people they online uh we are the resist and and we're just trying to fix the country
so
Speaker 57: for doing my common you know sense opinions i get death threats i've been swatted three times they try to have me murdered tell us
Speaker 67: well tell us what that's
like well it
Speaker 22: always usually happens during my podcast but so um
Speaker 57: the last time they they call and pretend to be me and they said that um
Speaker 57: That
Speaker 22: I caught my wife in bed with somebody and I'm not married so and I shot them both and then when the police get there I'm going to kill them so they'll try to come up and get you they try to get you murdered that's what it is it's attempted murder if you ask me
Speaker 68: during your podcast
Speaker 22: during the part it's always during the podcast it's happened to me three times it's happened to a lot of us you know it's happened to Marjorie Taylor Greene Tim Poole.
Speaker 22: but once you know everybody's once you get to a certain level they're gonna come after you I have they've lately they've been cutting heads off rabbits and throwing them off the body over
my gate
Speaker 41: series that's happened three times now - so
Speaker 69: we live in a country
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): where
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): The citizenry is surveilled much more thoroughly than North Korea surveils its own citizens. Like
Speaker 70: everything you do is monitored. Right. Through your phone, facial recognition, satellites, everything is monitored. But they can't find the people who are doing this?
Speaker 22: Yeah. And are they even interested in finding it if it happens to us? You know, I mean, who do we call? Who do you call? Who do you call? Because there is nobody.
Speaker 57: Now, the local police where I live are awesome. And I support the blue. I always have. I just don't support the feds at all. I mean, look,
Speaker 57: they've turned into
tucker it's
Speaker 73: it's it's it's awful so
Speaker 72: you call the local cops when this happens and what do they
say
Speaker 74: well the first time i did it they were like you're cat turd aren't you and so yeah so i i left them after the first time i gave them a bunch of gear you know
Speaker 22: here get some cat turd stuff but they they actually come and they patrol my property a lot mainly because it's a one-horse town there's nothing else to do yeah but uh they're great
Speaker 22: And they watch it like a hawk. You know, they're very protective of it. But it's
like if
Speaker 22: somebody on the left annoys me, which they
do a
Speaker 22: lot, I'll mute them. Right. If I annoy
Speaker 64: people, which I understand I do, they
try to have
Speaker 64: me killed. I mean, that's a big gap, isn't
Speaker 75: it? Right. It's a big gap. Muting. Yeah. Attempted murder. Big.
- So
Speaker 78: you spend your life watching what's happening.
Speaker 41: - Oh
Speaker 79: yeah. - What conclusions have you drawn? Where do you think we're going
this
Speaker 57: year? - Well, we're in trouble. I mean, it's just,
I always
Speaker 57: try to be positive, but sometimes I can't see a way out of it anymore. Can you? I mean, I just don't see a way out of it. And I'm a Trump supporter. I'm a Trump guy. - Yeah.
- If you,
Speaker 57: you know, I go back to the, it cracks me. The funniest thing to me on X is,
Speaker 57: all the people that do whatever the government says that put resist in their bio. That's the funniest thing. You know, Black Lives Matter. Obedient little bitches.
Speaker 81: Yeah, yeah, whatever.
And
Speaker 66: they can tell them anything and they'll do it. If you can convince your voters that men can have babies, think about that. You've got them. You've
Speaker 82: got them. You can tell them to wear a dirty dopper on their head and they're going to do it. They will. Well, they did, actually. You're
racist if
Speaker 82: you don't have a dirty dopper on
Speaker 84: your head.
Speaker 82: But once they
Speaker 83: can convince you of that,
Speaker 22: I mean, you've got to know these people are laughing when they're at the bar, the Democrats, saying that we've convinced them that men can have babies. And they believe it. And they're calling everybody names that doesn't believe it.
So do you see
Speaker 22: that changing at all?
I believe
Speaker 22: the woke part of it is coming to a head. I really do. I think people are tired of it. I am.
And we don't
Speaker 22: care what names you call us. And I'm a person who believes I don't.
Speaker 22: you know i was a hippie
i was
Speaker 22: a real hippie not one of these fake hippies don't lie i was an actual hippie i mean i lived up i was homeless at one time i lived up in a tent but in a lake for months how
Speaker 85: was it um it
Speaker 22: was good i could
Speaker 84: call a lot of crappy and i ate them every
night you a
Speaker 22: crappy every
Speaker 86: night oh
Speaker 22: well you gotta gotta eat somehow yeah
Speaker 52: so it's it's
Speaker 87: it's a it's a rough spot to be in but
Speaker 87: What were we talking about?
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): You're saying that people are getting sick of the anti-white stuff, the trans stuff, all
Speaker 22: that. But do kids have a chance? I mean, think about this, I'm 59, I think you're in your 50s, and we went to school there was,
you
Speaker 64: know, we actually learned mathematics, social studies, history, but they, think about a kid
Speaker 66: these days, he goes to school, they start when they're three or four in kindergarten, and they don't have a chance.
they
Speaker 66: they look what they do to them now they're like critical race theory you get over there all you're racist and you're okay you're racist and then they put a mask on you and and they they they teach you that the air you breathe is poison and then they tell you you're all going to die and burn in hellfire from global warming in 12 years think about these little kids how scared they are they scare the hell
Speaker 88: out of
Speaker 66: them yeah they do and then it's uh trans this and and and and they're showing BJ's to seven years old.
Speaker 22: books. And then they go through the whole school and it's like that. And then they step into college and what's college? It's turbo now. And they're brainwashed through. And I honestly think the longer you stay in college, the dumber
you get
Speaker 22: now. I honestly believe that. I don't
Speaker 89: think there's any question about it. Does that make sense? It makes a lot of
Speaker 66: sense. And so you have these teachers
Speaker 66: So they go they go through that and then they go and they stay in college as long as they can to the 30 years old and then they go right from there to a teaching job.
Speaker 22: So they stay on campus until they're 50. So
they don't
Speaker 22: have any life experience. They've never they don't know what
it's like
Speaker 22: to to work
Speaker 23: for a living or run a business. And they're the ones teaching, you know, and it's just it's horrible. So they don't have a chance.
Speaker 90: So.
All
Speaker 90: of this or some of it is going to come to a head this calendar year because of the presidential election. Oh,
Speaker 91: yeah. Where do you see that going?
Speaker 41: Well, man, Trump's going to win the primary. I hope
Speaker 22: everybody knows that. We can call him all around and fight each other and the DeSantis people. I'm in there. We're all fighting each other. But Trump's going to win the primary, and he should win it. But, man, what?
what
Speaker 22: they're doing to him and they're not they're not doing it to trump to do it to trump they hate him
Speaker 66: but i always say
on
Speaker 22: the podcast that washington's okay as long as they have george bush versus obama every year that's what they want they want george bush versus obama every four years they split up the four trillion dollars with their friends some of them get it sometimes some of them give it that's what they want they want bush versus obama they're okay with that They love Nikki Haley. Of course they do.
Speaker 22: - Can
I ask
Speaker 92: you to pause, and since you're online all day,
do you
Speaker 92: think there's organic support for Nikki Haley? - There's
none.
Speaker 37: - Okay, 'cause she's, I'm not even sure she's an actual human being. - Yeah, she's the most dangerous
Speaker 22: Republican primary candidate we've had, probably one of them in my lifetime. - Why'd you say that? - She's just, I mean, some of the things she said lately, she's a neocon, number one. I mean, my God.
How
Speaker 22: many times are you going to be fooled, America? I mean, from the Vietnam War, if North Vietnam beats South Vietnam, it's over for our country. So let's send
Speaker 66: 60,000 people to die. Korea was the same way, all the Middle Eastern
Speaker 94: wars, and she's right in there, Ukraine, Ukraine. But
Speaker 95: unlike you, she served our country in uniform—oh, wait.
Speaker 22: Oh, yeah.
Speaker 22: Yep. But she's dangerous. And remember when she said a week
Speaker 64: ago, if you're anonymous on Twitter, whatever, I want your name. That's what she said.
Speaker 96: You've got to register with the government to give your opinion.
Speaker 64: I want your name. Not the government
Speaker 22: wants it. I do. She's dangerous. I get a feel for people. I've always had a knack to kind of feel people
Speaker 64: out. And I just...
Speaker 64: It's just she's like Mike Pence. Yeah, she's nothing they say is authentic.
Speaker 22: Everything sounds like it's programmed cliches. Yes I've had a
lot of
Speaker 22: bosses in my life and some nasty ones, you know That's the way bosses are. Yeah, and every person I've ever talked to in my life and every boss ever had they talk exactly like Trump All of them. Yeah, I don't have anybody in my life that sets up there like Mike Pence and
Speaker 41: you know,
I
A
Speaker 41: bird in the hand's worth two in the bush. You know, just every cliche you can imagine. Do you get a creepy vibe off Pence?
Speaker 57: Total. I say on the podcast sometimes, I don't know what skeletons these days. I'd
Speaker 22: hate to see what goes on there when the lights
Speaker 57: go out of his house. Because
Speaker 99: it's
Speaker 22: just, nobody's that
Speaker 99: perfect. You know, quit acting perfect. I
remember
Speaker 100: that time he was like, I can't even have lunch with another woman because I'm married, even if we're
Speaker 101: friends. Remember when he said that? Yeah, that sounds like, yeah, I had a lot of thoughts about that.
I
Speaker 102: mean, by the way, I think if you're married, you should really actively try not to commit adultery. I think that's – I totally
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): agree with that 100%. But him specifically saying that, I reached exactly the opposite conclusion. I'm just going to say that.
Speaker 41: Yeah. I don't trust them when they're that perfect. And it's all – it's just like it's planned. Everything they
Speaker 103: say is planned. And I just –
Speaker 104: that's why I like Trump.
You
Speaker 104: know, does Trump make some bad? I don't believe everything you say. You don't believe everything I say. I don't believe Trump doesn't believe everything I say. But I
Speaker 64: mean, what they're doing now, he's already an iconic figure. They're going to turn him into a martyr. And they're making him more powerful and more powerful and more powerful. And
I could
Speaker 64: see him if the election was fair. I could see him just totally steamrolling. If it was fair, I know it would be.
Do you think
Speaker 105: it will be?
Speaker 64: Well, who do we have to fight? Who do we have to fight? Ronna McDaniels? Give me a break. I mean,
we got
Speaker 64: Scott Pressler out there beating the streets. He's beating the street like a bicycle clown out there. He is going around everywhere. He's registering voters. He's on the ground, and the Republican Party won't give him the time of day. He knows every rule to every county in this country.
And
Speaker 64: if you could have 1,000 of him out there and they trained
Speaker 107: another 1,000, you could sweep this thing.
Why do you think
Speaker 107: they're not doing
Speaker 32: that? Well, I mean,
why
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): would you have someone as mediocre and incapable as Ronna McDaniel who has no track record of success in any area? Why
would
Speaker 102: she run the Republican Party? That's pretty weird, right? I
Speaker 103: have no idea.
Speaker 103: when, you know, 90% of the people were complaining about her
Speaker 108: getting the job again. I remember one of the donors said, y'all, this has nothing to do with y'all, the donors picked this. I remember
Speaker 41: reading a story like that. - That sounds true. - It's true. They don't care. They don't care about us. I mean, I always say, especially when it comes to Trump,
Speaker 64: the Democrats will cheat and the Republicans will let him because they hate Trump.
-
Speaker 110: Yeah.
Speaker 64: - They hate
him.
And I
Speaker 64: mean it's a simple choice to me. I mean if you really he's the only resist president in my lifetime. Why do you think they
hate him so much?
Speaker 111: Because he's not a part of their club. This is not about
Trump to
Speaker 111: me. It's just
Speaker 64: like this is an outsider and we're going to destroy his life and we're going to show everybody out there
That if
Speaker 64: you pick an outsider, somebody that we hadn't picked, going back to a Bush versus Obama situation, if it's not the people we pick that we're okay with, we're going to destroy their lives. They can't even get a lawyer. They'll arrest your
Speaker 104: lawyer for
Speaker 64: defending you.
And
Speaker 110: we're
Speaker 64: going to make up stuff. We're going to say your property that's worth a billion dollars is worth $13.74. We're going to do whatever we can. And this is to show not just Trump, but to anybody in the next 50
years
Speaker 64: years, we will, the FBI, the CIA, we will destroy you if you're not our chosen people. And that's what I think
is going
Speaker 38: on. If Trump is prevented from appearing on the ballot
Speaker 112 (lower-pitched voice): in November, if he's arrested,
Speaker 70: you know, something even worse happens, which is entirely possible. That's the next step. Of course it's the next step. I don't even want to
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): say it out loud.
Speaker 113: Everyone knows. I
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): hate saying it, but it's true. No, of course. I'm not going to, but everyone knows what I'm
talking about.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): But if he is prevented, if democracy is prevented from proceeding, what
do you think
Speaker 62: the response from his voters is going to be since you follow this carefully? Well,
Speaker 108: why do you think they do the January 6th things? They want you scared that if you do anything, you could be 80 foot away outside the tape of the Capitol. You could be a half a mile away and they're going to come after
you.
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): Because there haven't been any, I mean, this used to be a country where people felt free to assemble, as is
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): guaranteed them in the Constitution, to make their views known. The demonstrations and rallies, you haven't seen, January 6th was the last one on the right that I'm aware of. That's
Speaker 114: what they're trying to do, scare you. So,
but
Speaker 115: do you think that there will be demonstrations if something...
Speaker 116: Oh, yeah, it's, yeah.
Speaker 117: But like
I say,
Speaker 117: they're just making it more powerful.
Yeah.
- Making
Speaker 57: Trump more powerful. - Yeah, I mean, I hate to tell you Libs this, but because of you, in a hundred
Speaker 51: years, they're not gonna be talking about me or even you, they're gonna be talking about Trump in a hundred years. - I agree with that. - He's gonna be one of the biggest figures in the history of our country.
Speaker 64: Not because of what he did, but because of how they're treating him. And they're making him more
Speaker 51: powerful. And if he gets arrested and gets put in a jail, can you
imagine?
And it
Speaker 51: could happen. People say it couldn't happen. Oh, it could happen. It could happen very easily. Yeah. Who should he pick as his running mate? Oh,
man, I go
Speaker 64: back and forth from this. I would like to say this, that I don't think the
Speaker 108: VP pick really matters
Speaker 51: that much. I mean, we got Harris as a VP that proves it. Right, yeah. But I'll
tell you,
Speaker 51: it takes a long time for me to trust you, but...
I'm
Speaker 51: starting to like Vivek, and I'm not sure if he's
Speaker 64: fake, and I'm not sure if it's just a show, but man, he's pissing them off as bad as
Speaker 119: me and you. Yeah,
they hate
Speaker 119: him.
Speaker 108: They do, and he's saying, I mean, boy, them debates, my God, he got Ronan McDougall, he got all of them mad. But he, and
isn't it
Speaker 108: funny?
Speaker 108: He's running
Speaker 104: the campaign exactly what DeSantis should have been running. He's running the campaign that DeSantis, but DeSantis is running a Nikki Haley
campaign. -
Speaker 104: Does it seem that way? - It does to
me. -
Speaker 104: Why? - I think you said something about his online team is just so
Speaker 120: cringe. - I
Speaker 104: shouldn't have said
Speaker 30 (lower-pitched voice): that. I shouldn't have gotten involved in that. I've been trying to stay out of it. - Well, they are.
Speaker 121: - I don't understand it.
And
Speaker 121: people like, you
Speaker 104: know, people build trust with you. It's
Speaker 64: consistency over time.
And
Speaker 122: when
Speaker 64: you're a Trump supporter, well, some of them hated Trump. Then you loved Trump and you loved him. And now you love DeSantis.
Speaker 104: And then if he's gone, you're going to love Nikki Haley. People don't trust that.
And I don't have
Speaker 64: anything against any of them. I
mute a
Speaker 64: lot of them.
Speaker 64: I don't carry grudges with these people and I welcome anybody in
Speaker 123: when it's over. Of
Speaker 64: course. I don't have any grudge.
Speaker 27: Do you think that, but it does seem, I mean, I don't follow it very closely, I'll admit, I don't want to follow it closely, but it does seem
Speaker 112 (lower-pitched voice): like there's enormous bitterness between the DeSantis people and the Trump people.
Speaker 74: Oh,
Speaker 51: there is. It's crazy. And I try not to get into the personal attacks. I'm kind of like Trump, even on X.
Speaker 51: If you want to, you know, I'm a shit poster. If you want to come at the shit poster with two million followers, come on, and an army of, you know, phone went out the mouth just waiting for me to say something, you know, to get on somebody. But I very
Speaker 64: seldom, I don't just attack first, but, you know, if you keep attacking me. Yeah. But it doesn't bother me. I don't take any of this stuff personally. I don't either. You know, they
call me
Speaker 64: every name in the book, you know.
Speaker 64: I'll be called, you know, you're old, you're fat, you're ugly. I mean, that's how they fight, you know, which all three are kind of true. I'll
have
Speaker 51: to beat them the next round. But people get so mad at this. And you have to, like, if...
you
Speaker 64: have to step back from it and i think
Speaker 108: it's funny i've lived in the real world where you know i've been in bar fights you know i have real you know stuff
um so you
Speaker 108: know somebody calling me ugly and old and a boomer uh i don't care yeah do you i don't
Speaker 125: care i don't even know what people say i i care what the people i love think that's
Speaker 60: me too and that's it um and like
Speaker 126: you have a lot of dogs which
Speaker 48: really helps yeah um do you think the breach
Speaker 48: Between those two camps, Trump-DeSantis can be fixed.
Speaker 64: Yeah, I think some of it, some people can't, but most people can. But this is my first primary. I mean, it's been – I don't know if it's ever been this vicious,
but –
So I
Speaker 64: supported DeSantis, I'm a Florida guy, and I was glad he was our governor. Oh, me too. I don't get paid by any campaign, and I pushed hard, and I was so glad when he won by 20 points, and I was so happy, and I think he's a good governor. Yeah. And so I try to tell people, I don't want him so beaten down and hammered that we end up getting a blue governor next, you know, a Gavin Newsom, destroy our state. I mean, you're here now.
Speaker 64: But someone from his team, not crazy high, but they asked me my honest opinion about it when he when he said he was going to run. And I was like, don't do it. Whatever you do, don't run. Think about it. And this is what I told him. I said, OK, he's 44. Young, young.
Speaker 128: Yeah. And
Speaker 64: he just won reelection by the biggest landslide.
I was
Speaker 73: like...
Speaker 129: - Governing your
Speaker 73: state. - Yeah, and how perfect is the timing? When the end of your eight years is up, it would be right getting in
Speaker 64: the meat of the 2028. - That's right. - This is what I tell them, support Trump, because he helped you. And you don't want the Trump supporters, they can destroy you. I mean, you don't want them, you know, you don't want to turn on them. I swear, I said, look, just please,
Speaker 64: this is my advice just having governor governor support trump all he can and in 28 you got biden with only four years left or trump with only four years left and
Speaker 73: now you're more popular and now you have all the trump people you have all the desantis people and you can moonwalk into the white house in 2028 moonwalk that's my
Speaker 130: exact words i use what was the response you
Speaker 73: got um yeah
Speaker 74: okay thanks
Speaker 74: A lot of people don't take me too seriously, and I hate it. I hate it's going like this.
A lot of
Speaker 131: people do
Speaker 48: take you seriously, which is interesting. It is. And I can see why. I think you're insightful. Thank you. How many politicians have
Speaker 103: you met personally? Well, personally, I kind of keep to myself, but DM-wise
Speaker 104: and message me,
Speaker 64: they all love me when it comes to election time. "Hey, will you retweet this and retweet this?"
Speaker 64: And I can't name five people in either party I trust. I just don't trust anybody anymore. And they don't deserve our trust. The Republican Party, I mean, come on. They don't know how to fight.
Speaker 132: - No, I
Speaker 64: know. - They're over there talking about their principles and they're arresting their political opponents. So you better get in the game. And we get the power of the gavel and what do they do with it? Seriously. - Nothing.
I
Speaker 64: mean, this is how you fight when you get the gavel. You do your own January 6th committee. But
Speaker 107: do you think it's because they don't understand how to fight or they're throwing the match? I don't know if they just don't
care or
Speaker 107: they don't know how or they're just
Speaker 64: cowards. But the truth is, see, this is how you fight. You get a January 6th committee and you don't allow any Democrats on it. And you put everybody on it they hate, just like they did us. You put Marjorie Taylor Greene, Boebert, Matt Gaetz. That's
Speaker 22: the January 6th committee. You don't allow them
to have
Speaker 22: any witnesses and you start subpoenaing let's see what nancy pelosi was talking to the capitol police you start saying everybody and you have
Speaker 64: it on c-span every day for years and if they if you don't start fighting
Speaker 49: like that it's over for this
Speaker 133: country well but and also
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): you have an obligation to that because it's in pursuit of the truth i know what do you make of the fact that the new speaker
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): of the house mike johnson
has
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): not released the videotape, which he controls.
Speaker 108: Well, I told everybody, you know, that he was going to be awful. I warned
Speaker 22: everybody that had that little kumbaya moment. What did he do? Exactly what Kevin McCarthy did. He said he's going
Speaker 64: to release it. So they get the big headlines, gets everybody excited. They release 1% of 1%, and
then they
Speaker 64: just don't do it anymore. And look what, when you release that, the Q Shaman,
He got
Speaker 49: out of prison because of that one little five minutes. Think of what if they were just release it, just release it. But they can't do it. It's just push the button, just push the button and release
Speaker 64: it. I know when he was talking about Ukraine funding, he's like, well, we have to at some point do the
Speaker 134: Ukraine funding because we don't want Russia steamrolling over Europe. That was his exact words or I'm paraphrasing close.
Speaker 135: I mean, obviously you'd have to be really stupid to believe that. I'm assuming he's not stupid. I mean,
Speaker 135: Why would he say something
Speaker 136: like that? - It's the same thing they always do to get us ginned up about a war.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): - Also, by the way, if Russia invaded Western Europe, could it be in worse shape than it is now? I mean, it was the US government that blew up the German economy. It wasn't the Russians. It was the Biden administration that blew up Nord Stream. - Oh yeah.
Speaker 12: - And ended their main source of cheap energy. So like, could the Russians be worse than that? Maybe, I guess, but
like...
I don't
Speaker 108: get it. Well, you know, they've used Ukraine as kind of their 51st state, and they would know rules. The bio labs, which they lied about and told the truth. Everybody in Washington, their kids over there making $4 million a year, you know, at
Speaker 64: some kind of company. But...
Speaker 64: I don't let them gin me up, and they try to gin you up more and get you mad. I can't get emotional when we have 100,000 people dying of fentanyl poisoning in
Speaker 137: our own country. I'm not
Speaker 64: going to get emotional. I hate war. I'm anti-war. I'm the one that wants a peace deal. You're the one that wants to keep. And here's the problem with Ukraine.
Speaker 64: I think we're going to end up in the same
Speaker 108: spot a year or so from now. I think there's going to be a peace agreement at some point, and there's going to be a million dead people, and Russia's going to take a little bit of the country, and we're going to be in the same place we would have
Speaker 64: been.
And
Speaker 7: no one will ever apologize for all those dead.
Speaker 64: they're just going to call us Putin puppets because we want peace, and that's it.
Speaker 7: Couldn't agree
Speaker 104: more. So
first of
Speaker 138: all,
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): thank you for doing this. I appreciate it. No
Speaker 139: problem.
Last
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): question. So you went from installing FiberLine...
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): to becoming legitimately famous only because of your voice. You were allowed to talk in public purely democratically. People liked what you said, they supported you. All of that is contingent on having a voice. Do you think a year from now you will have the same voice? You will be allowed to
Speaker 71: say the things that you are saying
now?
Speaker 64: Well, I hope so. But you see what they're doing to come after me. You know, I hate to say this, but I tell my family all the
Speaker 108: time, hey, the FBI can frame
me.
who
Speaker 108: know i mean i don't trust
them no
Speaker 108: and i hate saying that i want an fbi that i don't feel that way about but hey um that you know they can do anything they can if they want to get me
Speaker 74: they're
going to get me
Speaker 74: but i'm not going to
shut up
Speaker 74: so that's
it i'm
Speaker 74: not shutting up so do
Speaker 112 (lower-pitched voice): you feel that you will be able to reach the same audience a year from
now i i
Speaker 64: think so i mean it's it's gone up um
Speaker 64: And I'm, you know,
Speaker 108: I'm doing my own events now. We're doing, we did turd stock. I didn't want to mention that, which
Speaker 51: was, it was kind of a, John Rich and I was kind of a joke. And I said, no, I'm serious. Instead of, you know, Woodstock, let's do turd stock.
Where'd you
Speaker 140: do it?
Speaker 108: Yeah, at the Redneck Riviera up at his place in November. That's my big coming out where everybody got to see me. And I
Speaker 57: had some great musicians. We're actually, one of the musicians, Angie Apero,
Speaker 57: who has got a—you'd love this story, Tucker. It's the great American comeback story. He wrote A Cry for Faith Hill, and she won a Grammy.
And he was
Speaker 57: this, like, unbelievable musician with his voice. And he was on his way up, signed with a record label, and then he had a stroke and completely
Speaker 22: lost his voice and couldn't talk. And so he spent—
Speaker 22: I think it's 2016, 2017, learn how to talk again. And so now he's on his way back up and he was there. And we're doing an event for him on the 24th. So I'm going to just keep kind of staying in my lane and just do what I do. I probably won't go into the red carpet events to meet everybody and get pictures.
Speaker 22: So we're going
Speaker 51: to miss
Speaker 141: you at Davos next week.
Speaker 51: I'm not going to be
Speaker 33: there. You're not going to be there? Yeah, I don't know. I
Speaker 22: just don't seem like I fit in there to me. I'm more of the hanging out with the people kind of person. But it was nice to meet you,
Speaker 87: and I really appreciate you inviting me.
Speaker 142: We're grateful to have you. Cat turd.
Thank
Speaker 87: you.
Speaker 143: Free speech is bigger than any one person or any one organization. Societies are defined by what they will not permit. What we're watching is the total inversion of virtue.